Hello Hello Friends Welcome back to my
YouTube channel Technical and Friend In today's
video I am going to give you some important updates related to ICICI Bank
What is that important update in this video, you should
watch the video and then you will understand, so
in Dubai we will talk
about those Home Guards Surat Police,
ICICI Bank has given some important updates related to its Choice Number Police,
due to this virus now if the insured gets
his treatment done at home
then his expenses will be covered in this
and the voting period on police has been removed and reduced to
15 days, the company will
continue to offer no claim bonus in these cases also
and keeping in mind the coronavirus epidemic, Notary General Insurance has
given full facilities to its customers,
under this now if we get
our treatment done at home instead of the graveyard then its expenses will also be
covered in the insurance, it will be of
great benefit to you, who want to get treatment for any disease
in a safe environment at home instead of the hospital and the
voting period is of 15 days  The
voting period for police has been
reduced to 15 days, which was earlier
daily. It is a good thing that there has been no increase
in the free voting period for reduction in fees.
This will be
applicable to all health policies and
also to claims related to witnesses. No Claim Bonus: In the
case of John Tyndall, the Baby No Claim Bonus will
continue to be offered. If the insured is
admitted to the hospital on these records, the
accumulated additional sum insured in the policy will
not be affected. Thus,
necessary financial relief is being provided to the policyholder.
This is a festival complaint. The insurance and
health booklet is given in the skin. If you do
not take any action, then the company will
give you a no claim bonus. The cover in this is
valid up to ₹5000 this year. The coverage will be from ₹1000 to ₹5000.
ICICI
Lombard phone number is
not for dealing with this. Suresh brought the police. Police has been
launched in group insurance mode.
Under this policy, the insurance company will pay the entire amount in case of
corona virus being confirmed at any government travel centre. The
sum insured will be deducted during the policy period.  You should know
that one will be given free of cost with these, keep giving it to you
and in the language Chaudhary said that
you will get the initial waiting period for this, this is cut
off and for one year, these people
also tweet about flood, the insurance amount of the Protection Forum is
₹3000 and its premium is ₹150, if
you have also taken a shadow banking
insurance policy even if it is not bad and you have any
health risk, if you should stay at home then
this can be very beneficial for you,
so if you like this video of mine
then like my video, share it, if you
come to my channel for the first time then you
must subscribe to the channel, in this way
Suresh Lohar will give you that bank - later
in this video, till then thank you friends